Prince Singh

Full Stack Web-Developer



♀ Bangalaore , karnataka in Prince Singh ► Portfolio

mrprincesingh



EDUCATION

Full Stack Web development

Masai School

04/2022 – present | Bangalore, Karnataka

Full time Course

12th

Narayana Pu College

04/2016 - 04/2018 | Bangalore, Karnataka



TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML-5 || CSS-3 || JAVASCRIPT(JS) ||Git|| JSON || REACT JS || REDUX || CHAKRA UI || NETLIFY || GITHUB|| MONGO DB|| DATA STRUCTURES AND ALGORITHM || BOOTSTRAP



♀ SOFT SKILLS

Leadership Skills, Problem solving Skills ,Communication Skills



PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

FSL - First-Source-Pvt-LTD

Customer Care Executive

09/2021 - 03/2022 | Bangalore, India

Worked as a customer care executive Inbond at First Source PVT LTD in a process called Bank of Baroda

BPO Convergence

Customer Care Executive

03/2021 - 09/2021 | Delhi, india

Worked as a customer care executive Inbound at BPO CONVERGENCE in a process called SHIPROCKET

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Full-Stack Developer with expertise in Optimization, designing and maintaining Web Applications and systems, writing and Debugging optimized code, and utilizing multiple front-end languages and libraries. With a focus on independent product platform functionality Testing, developing digital solutions that meet specific Business Operations.

PROJECTS

DERMSTORE CLONE $\mathscr D$

Check Live 🔗

Tech Stack:-HTML || CSS || JAVASCRIPT|| BOOTSTRAP ||

DermStore is an E-commerce platform offering Optimization professional-strength Design Thinking formulas from top skin care brand A collaborative project built by a team of 5 executed in 4 days

Area of Responsibility

- · worked on Navbar
- worked on Footer
- Cart Page
- · Checkout Page

Features

- · Attractive Navbar
- Calculations / Delete Product

Airtable.com - Clone &

Check Live &

Tech Stack :- HTML-5 || CSS-3 || JAVASCRIPT || React || Redux || Chakra UI

Airtable is a Software Development Task Management tool, People around the world use. Airtable to do everything from cattle tracking to filmmaking. Collaborative project built by a team of 5 and executed in 4 days.

Area of Responsibility

- Login Page
- resource page
- Single Resource page

Features

- Features
- Login functionality with complete form validation

Caratlane.com 🔗

Check Live 🔗

Tech Stack:- HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, ES6, chakra-ui, ReactJS, Redux, MongoDB Atlas, nodejs, express js, REST

It was a teamwork of 4 members which was completed within 5days, CaratLane is e-commerce website which is specialized in Jewellery Product (Also played a Role of team lead and managed the whole project)

Area of Responsibility

- worked on complete Backend(CRUD)
- worked on the complete admin side(CRUD)

Features

- Used MongoDB Atlas as a database
- implemented Complete CRUD operation both in Backend and Frontend